http://www.jondon.com/privacy/

Menu
COVID-19EquipmentAir Movers / FansAir Scrubbers / Negative Air MachinesCarpet Cleaning EquipmentConcrete EquipmentDehumidifiersDuct CleaningFlood / Water ExtractionFloor Cleaning EquipmentMeters and Testing ToolsOdor Control EquipmentTile and Grout CleaningTruck Mounts and AccessoriesVacuumsWands, Upholstery and Stair ToolsFloor and Cavity DryingPortable HeatersPower Distribution / ElectricalRepair and Carpet Installation ToolsUpholstery Cleaning Ultrasonic Cleaning EquipmentSupplies & AccessoriesBrushes, Brooms and BonnetsBuckets and ContainersCarpet Groomers and RakesConcrete SuppliesContainmentDispensersDuctingDusting and Dust MopsExtension Poles / HandlesFiltersFloor PadsFoam Blocks and TabsFurniture MovingGlovesHand ToolsHoses and Hose AccessoriesJanitor Carts and OrganizersMattingMopping SuppliesPaper ProductsPoly SheetingRags, Sponges, Towels, WipesRestroom SuppliesSafety / PPESandscreens, Sand Paper, AbrasivesScrapers and BladesSprayers and Spray BottlesSqueegees, Smoothers, ApplicatorsTape and Masking SuppliesTrash Bags, Containers, LinersTrash Receptacles and AccessoriesVacuum BagsWindow CleaningChemicalsAbatement, Restoration, RemediationCarpet Cleaning ChemicalsFloor Care ChemicalsConcrete ChemicalsCleaners and DegreasersDeodorizers / Odor ControlDisinfectants and SanitizersFire, Smoke, and Soot CleanersSpot and Stain RemoversUpholstery CleanersGlass CleanersLaundry ProductsRestroom Cleaners and DeodorizersStone CareUltrasonic ChemicalsAviation CleaningCustom Label ProductsHand and Skin CareInsecticidesMetal and Furniture PolishSpray Foam Sealants / InsulationSafetyContainmentCoveralls and
Protective Clothing Respiratory ProtectionEye Protection / Safety GogglesGloves / Hand ProtectionHearing ProtectionFall ProtectionFloor Signs / Barrier TapeFirst AidSpill Control / Chemical SafetyParts Shop by BrandBearings BeltsCasters and WheelsElectricalEngine PartsFiltersFittings and ValvesFluids and LubricantsFuel Tap KitsGaskets and SealsGaugesHeat ExchangersHoses (Replacement)MotorsPumpsSqueegees & BrushesSpray Guns & WandsSpray Nozzles / JetsTriggers & LeversVacuum Bags / PartsVacuum MotorsValvesEducationHow-to / Technical GuidesMarketing & Sales AidsEducational ProductsSeminarsClearanceCarpet Cleaning Clearance Janitorial ClearanceRestoration ClearanceConcrete Clearance
Account
30-Day Money-Back Guarantee
Dedicated Customer Service Team
Same-Day Shipping
Home
Your Privacy
Jon-Don Privacy Policy
By
accessing or using this website, you agree to this Privacy Policy. This Privacy
Policy may change from time to time. Your continued use of Jon-Don’s website
after Jon-Don makes changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so
please check this Privacy Policy periodically for updates.
I. Personal
Information Collected
We may collect
personal identification from users in a variety of ways, including, but not
limited to, when users visit the site, register on the site, place an order,
fill out a form, respond to a survey, subscribe to a newsletter and in
connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make
available on our website anonymously.
How do we collect your data?
The following are examples of the
ways in which information may collected:
Directly from
you (e.g., during account registration, filling out a form, subscription to
emails).
Indirectly from
you (e.g., observing your actions on the website)
From third
parties (e.g., third party social networking providers, data aggregators,
affiliates)
From publicly
available sources (e.g., online database searches)
What data do we collect?
The following are examples of the
types of personal information collected:
Information
you provide: name, email address, mailing address (billing and shipping), phone
number, transaction information, payment card information, etc.
Information
associated with the use of our site: information gathered from cookies and web
pixels, such as IP address and interactions on the website to enhance your
experience on our website, aggregations of multiple visits to the website, chat
information
Non-personal
identification information: the browser / system information, the technical
information about users means of connection to our site, such as the operating
system and the Internet service provider(s) utilized and other similar
information.
How will we use your data?
We use your personal information for the following purposes:
Fulfill the order and delivery of products
Live chat and servicing an order or inquiry
Account activation and maintenance
Identify users to deliver marketing
materials
Analytics, business trends, and insights
Interaction on social media
We may share your personal data with one or more of the third
parties described here: vendors, service providers and consultants that perform
services on our behalf, companies which store and process data on our behalf,
companies which perform data analytics for us, companies which help deliver and
track our products, companies which send you information about products on our
behalf, and companies which you request us to share your personal information
with.
More specifically, we use Hotjar in order to better
understand our users’ needs and to optimize this service and experience.  Hotjar is a technology service that helps us
better understand our users’ experience (e.g. how much time they spend on which
pages, which links they choose to click, what users do and don’t like, etc.)
and this enables us to build and maintain our service with user feedback.  Hotjar uses cookies and other technologies to
collect data on our users’ behavior and their devices.  This includes a device's IP address (processed
during your session and stored in a de-identified form), device screen size,
device type (unique device identifiers), browser information, geographic
location (country only), and the preferred language used to display our website.
Hotjar stores this information on our
behalf in a pseudonymized user profile.  Hotjar
is contractually forbidden to sell any of the data collected on our behalf.
We also engage a third-party partner for the
purpose of identifying users and delivering to them marketing on our behalf
(i.e. email or direct mail).  Our
partners may collect information directly from your device, such as your IP
address, device ID, and information about your browser or operating system; may
combine personal and non-personal information about you with information from
other sources, and may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. This
activity enables them to identify you to facilitate the delivery of marketing
on our behalf. To opt out of recognition services, please go to https://idx.listrakbi.com/opt-out.html.  To opt out of third-party cookies, please go
to http://www.aboutads.info/choices.”
II.
Data Retention
When you place an order through the website, we
will maintain your order information for our records unless and until you ask
us to delete this information.
III. Communications
We may use your personal information to contact you with
newsletters, marketing, or promotional materials.  By subscribing to Jon-Don mobile messages,
you agree to receive autodialed marketing messages to the telephone number used
at the time of opt in.
To
opt out of mobile messages, Text STOP to 25850.
Sometimes we use a third party provider to send
email.  If you subscribe to any of our
email programs, the third party will have access to your email address for the
purposes of sending out correspondence pertaining to Jon-Don, and has no
authorization to use your email address for any purpose other than sending
messages from us to you.
If you have subscribed to our email programs and
wish to unsubscribe, you may do so at any time by using the unsubscribe link on
the bottom of any email message we send, or by managing your email preferences here: http://www.jondon.com/email/update-preferences.
IV. Cookies
Cookies are files placed on your computer to collect
standard Internet log information and visit behavior information.  You can instruct your browser to refuse all
cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent though some features of the
website require cookies.  When you visit
Jon-Don’s website, we may collect information from you automatically through
cookies or similar technology in order to enhance and personalize your online
experience, and permit us to remember you when you return to our website, to
deliver personalized marketing, and to better understand the way you use our
website.  For further information about
cookies visit allaboutcookies.org/.
V.
Data Collection
We collect information using the following technologies in
order to analyze the functionality and effectiveness of the website, to measure
the performance of a marketing effort on our behalf, including email marketing,
or to place advertising on our behalf across the Internet.
- “Cookies” as explained above.
- “Log files” track actions occurring on the website,
and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service
provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.
- “Web beacons”, “tags”, and “pixels” are
electronic files used to record information about how you browse the website.
VI. “Do Not Track”
Signals
Jon-Don’s website
does not support Do Not Track (DNT) at this time.  DNT is a privacy preference you can set in
your web browser to indicate that you do not want certain information about
your web page visits tracked and collected across websites.  For more details, including how to turn on Do
Not Track, visit www.donottrack.us.
VII. Security
The security of
your personal information is important to us, but remember that no method of
transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100%
secure. We strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal
information.
VIII. Your Rights
To the extent a specific element of our processing of
your personal information relies upon your consent, you may withdraw such
consent at any time.  Such a withdrawal
will not affect the lawfulness of the processing prior to the consent
withdrawal.
If you wish to object to the processing of your personal
data on the basis of legitimate interest and no opt-out mechanism is available
to you directly, please contact us.
If you do not provide us with certain portions of your
personal data, we may not be able to fulfill the requested purpose of
collection, such as to respond to your queries.
However, unless otherwise specified, not providing your personal data
will not result in legal consequences for you.
IX. Exercise your Rights
If you have any questions, please contact us:
By Postal Mail:
Jon-Don, LLC
Attention: Privacy Official
400 Medinah Rd
Roselle, Il 60172
By Phone:
1.800.400.9473
By email:
support@jondon.com
Jon-Don knows your privacy is important. We will not sell or share any personal information you provide us to any other organization without your express consent. We understand that your personal information is given to us to provide you with communications you have requested and for purchasing and shipping purposes- we respect that. If you have any questions, please call us at 1.800.400.9473.
Jon-Don uses third-party service providers to display ads on our behalf across the Internet. They may collect anonymous information about your visits to our Website, and your interaction with our products and services. They may also use information about your visits to this and other Websites to serve advertisements for goods and services. This anonymous information is collected through the use of pixel tags and cookies, which are internet standards used by most major web sites.
If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this anonymous information utilized by third party service providers, please visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/
We use Hotjar in order to better understand our users’ needs and to optimize this service and experience. Hotjar is a technology service that helps us better understand our users’ experience (e.g. how much time they spend on which pages, which links they choose to click, what users do and don’t like, etc.) and this enables us to build and maintain our service with user feedback. Hotjar uses cookies and other technologies to collect data on our users’ behavior and their devices. This includes a device's IP address (processed during your session and stored in a de-identified form), device screen size, device type (unique device identifiers), browser information, geographic location (country only), and the preferred language used to display our website. Hotjar stores this information on our behalf in a pseudonymized user profile. Hotjar is contractually forbidden to sell any of the data collected on our behalf.
Sometimes we use a third party provider to send email. If you subscribe to any of our email programs, the third party will have access to your email address for the purposes of sending out correspondence pertaining to Jon-Don, and has no authorization to use your email address for any purpose other than sending messages from us to you.
If you have subscribed to our email programs and wish to unsubscribe, you may do so at any time by using the unsubscribe link on the bottom of any email message we send, or by managing your email preferences here: http://www.jondon.com/email/update-preferences
You can also contact us directly.
By Postal Mail:Jon-Don, LLCAttention: Privacy Official400 Medinah RdRoselle, Il 60172By Phone:1.800.400.9473By email:support@jondon.com
